const cQuestions = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What does 'printf()' function do in C?",
        "choices": ["Prints a message to the console", "Reads input from the user", "Performs mathematical calculations"],
        "correctAnswer": "Prints a message to the console"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is a 'pointer' in C?",
        "choices": ["Variable that holds memory address", "Data type for characters", "Special function"],
        "correctAnswer": "Variable that holds memory address"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is 'malloc()' used for in C?",
        "choices": ["Memory allocation", "Mathematical operations", "File input/output"],
        "correctAnswer": "Memory allocation"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What does 'void' mean in a function declaration in C?",
        "choices": ["No return type", "Return type is unknown", "Function is empty"],
        "correctAnswer": "No return type"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is 'scanf()' function used for in C?",
        "choices": ["Prints formatted output", "Allocates memory", "Reads formatted input"],
        "correctAnswer": "Reads formatted input"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is the purpose of 'break' statement in C?",
        "choices": ["Terminate loop", "Skip to next iteration", "Exit program"],
        "correctAnswer": "Terminate loop"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is a 'struct' in C?",
        "choices": ["Data type to hold multiple elements", "Special function", "Data type for string"],
        "correctAnswer": "Data type to hold multiple elements"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What is 'typedef' used for in C?",
        "choices": ["Defines new data types", "Allocate memory", "Format output"],
        "correctAnswer": "Defines new data types"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What is 'const' keyword used for in C?",
        "choices": ["Define constant values", "Loop iteration", "Function declaration"],
        "correctAnswer": "Define constant values"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is the role of 'include' directive in C?",
        "choices": ["Include libraries", "Define constants", "Create loops"],
        "correctAnswer": "Include libraries"
    },
];
export default cQuestions;
